<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ted Parvu</title><link>https://ted.parvu.net/</link><description>Recent content on Ted Parvu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ted.parvu.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://ted.parvu.net/ted_parvu_C_developer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ted.parvu.net/ted_parvu_C_developer/</guid><description>Ted Parvu - Senior C Developer ted@tedstechshack.com | Mobile: +1-218-235-4303 Summary With over 20 years of professional experience, I possess a wide breadth of skills and knowledge that enable me to perceive how complex systems behave and interact. From the fundamentals of TCP/IP programming to security situational awareness, I have the experience to understand complex systems and their interactions.
Sample Work Experience February 2021 - May 2021 Titan Industries — Fully distributed team (Ely, Minnesota)</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ted.parvu.net/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ted.parvu.net/about/</guid><description>About My fascination with computing started in 1981 when my parent&amp;rsquo;s gave me a Sinclair ZX-81. I attended college at the University of Arizona where I was privileged to work with world-renowned optical scientists and astronomers. Over time I became an Open Source, Privacy, and Security advocate. For as long as I can remember, I have been in love with the natural world. That love has grown into a passion to defend the environment.</description></item><item><title>Ted Parvu - Computer Security Specialist</title><link>https://ted.parvu.net/ted_parvu_security_resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ted.parvu.net/ted_parvu_security_resume/</guid><description>Ted Parvu - Computer Security Specialist ted@tedstechshack.com | Mobile: +1-218-235-4303 Summary With over 20 years of professional experience, I possess a wide breadth of skills and knowledge that enable me to perceive how complex systems behave and interact. From the fundamentals of TCP/IP programming to security situational awareness, I have the experience to understand complex systems and their interactions. This awareness enables me to see vulnerabilities and attack surfaces others may overlook.</description></item><item><title>Ted Parvu’s Curriculum Vitae</title><link>https://ted.parvu.net/ted_parvu_CV/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ted.parvu.net/ted_parvu_CV/</guid><description>Ted Parvu&amp;rsquo;s Curriculum Vitae Computer Security, Blockchain, DevOps, Wildlife Advocate, Egalitarian
+1-218-235-4303 | ted@tedstechshack.com | GitHub | keybase.io | LinkedIn About My fascination with computing started in 1981 when my parent&amp;rsquo;s gave me a Sinclair ZX-81. I attended college at the University of Arizona where I was privileged to work with world-renowned optical scientists and astronomers. Over time I became an Open Source, Privacy, and Security advocate. For as long as I can remember, I have been in love with the natural world.</description></item></channel></rss>